{
    "id": "71719af2912c422daf9834dbfd420b15",
    "title": "Can, Could, May, Might",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. swim across the river.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a12a18fd528f4fbfa1d00bb1885b5b1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you lift this box?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebba246752ee474c9e81332ce6c8991a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I come in?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48dcb6b9c0b34c6582c0fb09a2d9985c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I borrow your bicycle?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2ad2d8383aba4af7b2c9b7a0caf146f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………… rain in the evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a1f3967194d4137b52fd824ffe772bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. this be true?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "055aa21b134249cfb66e83442bb3e397"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………… not be true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "may not",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "005808e9482240ca93feb3833ff23cba"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you find love and happiness!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a1a0e480d9a2452bb3e256cf6007fd69"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. swim across the river when I was young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "might",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3965149f46da4cf4aa374781ee8e7d7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ……………… come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6157bfb446aa4b21b5f88bb6cd7416db"
        }
    ]
}